<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright 2004-2013 ICEsoft Technologies Canada Corp.
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the
  ~ License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~ http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
  ~ software distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS
  ~ IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either
  ~ express or implied. See the License for the specific language
  ~ governing permissions and limitations under the License.
  -->

<renderer>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[
        <p>The outputConnectionStatus component displays the information about the status of the network connection
        between the client browser and the server. The component displays one of 4 possible states, which are as
        follows.
        <p>
           1. Active: The connection is alive and there is a request pending.<br/>
           2. Inactive: The connection is alive and there is no pending activity.<br/>
           3. Caution: The connection request/response latency has exceeded the configured threshold.
           Indicates that asynchronous updates from the server may not be received in a timely manner.<br/>
           4. Disconnected: The connection has been lost, either due to network or application error
           (session expiry, etc.).<br/>
        <p>
        The outputConnectionStatus component provides an ideal mechanism to provide continuous real-time feedback
        to users of the status of their ICEfaces application. It is particularly important to inform users when the
        application is busy sending and receiving data in response to a user-initiated action to manage their 
        expectations with respect to application readiness for additional user input. Generally, the
        outputConnectionStatus component should be located in a consistent location throughout an ICEfaces application.
        <p>
        NOTE: A web-page may only contain a single outputConnectionStatus component. Using more than one 
        outputConnectionStatus component on the same web page will result in erratic results.
         ]]>
	</description>
	<component-family>javax.faces.Panel</component-family>

	<renderer-type>
		com.icesoft.faces.OutputConnectionStatusRenderer
	</renderer-type>

	<renderer-extension>
		<instance-name>outputConnectionStatus</instance-name>
		<is-container>false</is-container>
		<renders-children>false</renders-children>
		<tag-name>outputConnectionStatus</tag-name>
		<taglib-prefix>@taglib-prefix@</taglib-prefix>
		<taglib-uri>@taglib-uri@</taglib-uri>
	</renderer-extension>

</renderer>
